{
    "subject": "resource/Edmund_Boulter",
    "predicate": "property/years",
    "object": "1698",
    "human_readable": "Edmund Boulter lived in 1698.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7836117744445801,
            "question": "In what year did Edmund Boulter live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7658082842826843,
            "question": "Where did Edmund Boulter live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5931858420372009,
            "question": "Were there any notable figures who lived around the same time as Edmund Boulter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5549950003623962,
            "question": "Is there any further information available about Edmund Boulter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5214878916740417,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about people who lived in 1698?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5130739212036133,
            "question": "What was life like for people living in 1698?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4879031181335449,
            "question": "What is known about Edmund Boulter's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34026387333869934,
            "question": "Were there any significant events happening in the world during Edmund Boulter's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1996452957391739,
            "question": "How did society change between 1698 and today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19700194895267487,
            "question": "What can we learn from studying historical figures like Edmund Boulter?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edmund Boulter lived in 1698.",
            "html": "dbpedia_931_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did society change between 1698 and today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_931_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant events happening in the world during Edmund Boulter's lifetime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_931_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Edmund Boulter's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_931_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_931_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_931_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_931_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_931_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_931_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_931_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_931_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_931_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_931_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_931_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that Edmund Boulter was elected Member of Parliament for the parliamentary borough of Boston, Lincolnshire in 1698. Therefore, it is supported by the information in the documents that Edmund Boulter lived in 1698."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Edmund Boulter was elected Member of Parliament for the parliamentary borough of Boston, Lincolnshire, in 1698. This supports the statement that Edmund Boulter lived (or more specifically, held a position) in 1698."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}